



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Skilled customer service executive with experience in medical administration, retail and hospitality. Recently worked in Sales and construction in quick succession due to the COVID-19 pandemic. Hoping to find a position to help excel my career.

CONTACT DETAILS

- Mobile: 089-9742200
- Email: seanrobert2010@gmail.com

QUALIFICATIONS

Leaving certificate. Ardgillan Community Coolege, Balbriggan, Co. Dublin. (271 CAO points) 2012-2017

Awards & Achievements

Oct 2010-Jan 2011: The Smile Project, a charity for children in developing countries

- Backpacked for the charity raising over €3000
- Helped fund raise a tour of schools and orphanages in Nepal teaching the Arts and English
- Aided in setting up a fundraising "Buskathon" to raise further funds needed for the organisation

Jan 2009 - 2011: Hope For Nikita

- · Promoted events for the charity
- Conducted street collections
- Helped sound engineer for many of the events
- Occasionally performed and filled in to acts when required

Achievements:

- 2015 Won the schools Leinster Cricket League
- 2015 Captain of Ardgillan school's cricket team
- 2010 O'Dwyers GAA club Most Dedicated Player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Appointment Centre Executive

Affidea Diagnostics (August 2018 - November 2019

- Providing a high-quality customer service experience through answering incoming calls, emails and faxes
- Resolving a high percentage of queries during initial contact. (first call resolution)
- Worked on RIS system contacting out of date referrals and fixing internal mistakes to ensure systems fluidity
- Processed payments for scans in advance through Medserv software.

Sales Executive & Construction Laborer (Due to COVID)

Sales Sense (March 2020 - July 2020) Suir Engineering (August 2020 - October 2020)

- Door to door sales working as a field representative
- Grew exceptional communication & engagement skills in a difficult and at first unknown environment
- Trained in on-site COVID 19 compliance and regulations due to current situation
- Learning a mixture of trades due to the variation in required work onsite.
- Demanded great planning skills due to the array of trades over a large site

Catering Assistant

SuperMacs (December 2017- March 2018

- Became qualified at the Prerequisite Hygiene Requirements under the
 HACCP
- Required excellent organisation skills in relation to handling stock and delivering orders
- Learned to use a cash register and deal with multiple customers simultaneously
- Involved quickly learning food preparation protocols and inter-personal skills in a hectic environmen